<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recent &amp; Upcoming Talks on Pleotonic Engineering</title>
    <link>/talk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recent &amp; Upcoming Talks on Pleotonic Engineering</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 Benito Palacios Sánchez</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/talk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Destripando juegos: protecciones anti ROM Hacking</title>
      <link>/talk/airorom-jasyp18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 02:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/airorom-jasyp18/</guid>
      <description>Talk at the JASyP (Jornadas de Anonimato, Seguridad y Privacidad). Organized by the group Interferencias in the University of Granada. I talked about the security mechanisms like encryption that we can find inside of the video-games with the goal to obfuscate their files to avoid hacks, mods and fan-translations.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ROM Hacking Level 01: Textos</title>
      <link>/talk/rh01-texts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 02:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/rh01-texts/</guid>
      <description>Live streaming from the virtual reality platform AltspaceVR. The talk explains different topics and concept related to text formats like encodings, tables, fonts and compression.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ROM Hacking Level 02: Imágenes</title>
      <link>/talk/rh02-imgs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 02:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/rh02-imgs/</guid>
      <description>Live streaming from Twitch requested by the TraduSquare community. This time I talked about the file format of the images, sprites and textures in video-games and all the kind of compression and techniques used in the Nintendo DS.
  Following this talk, the next day I did a second live streaming where the people choose three games for Nintendo DS and I had to figure out the image formats:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>El misterio de las claves de Pokémon Mundo Misterioso</title>
      <link>/talk/pokemon-mystery-devfestjaen18/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/pokemon-mystery-devfestjaen18/</guid>
      <description>Talk at the DevFest 2018 organized by the GDG Jaén (Google Developer Group). The presentation is about a Twitter thread I did on July. For a week I was figuring out how the game Pokémon Mistery Dungeon Explorers of Sky from Nintendo DS generate and validate a kind of password for rescue missions, special events and object sharing. It almost a study of the assembly code of the game with some notes about the implementation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Protocolos del Industrial IoT</title>
      <link>/talk/iiot-dds/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talk/iiot-dds/</guid>
      <description>Talk at the IEEE Developer Days organized by the association IEEE Student Branch of Elche. I talked about the Industrial Internet of Things (IIoT) and the main network protocols and framework in the market. I gave details on how one of them, DDS, works with a demo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>