<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Pleotonic Engineering</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Pleotonic Engineering</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 Benito Palacios Sánchez</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 02:01:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dissertation</title>
      <link>/project/airorom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 02:01:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/airorom/</guid>
      <description>Data Protection Mechanisms in Video Games Grade: 9.9 / 10
 Electrical Engineering Bachelor dissertation. I researched different video games of Nintendo DS to find out how they were protecting different sensitive content like text, video and audio to avoid modifications and/or access. I documented the different algorithms, their weakness and several recommendations to improve the protection.
 Project code name: AiroRom. Report PDF Presentation Slides Source code Wiki with temporal results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IV Tech Challenge</title>
      <link>/project/tech-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 02:01:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/tech-challenge/</guid>
      <description>Our team won the challenge!
 As part of a group of four students named Prometheus, we participated in an event organized by our university: University of Granada. We participated in the four edition of the so called Tech Challenge. It was sponsored by the company RTI who proposed the topic of the challenge: &amp;ldquo;create a distributed video system&amp;rdquo;. The goal was to simulate a start-up and create from scratch a prototype ready to go to the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ni no kuni: El mago de las tinieblas</title>
      <link>/project/ninokuni/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 02:01:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/ninokuni/</guid>
      <description>As a member of the GradienWords fan-translation group, I worked in my free time as Localization Engineer to translate from Japanese to Spanish the game: &amp;ldquo;Ni no kuni: Shikkoku no Madoshi&amp;rdquo; for Nintendo DS. In this altruistic project we did reverse engineering in the game to translate all the text and images files as well as edit font files and assembly code.
     Programming:  Create programs to convert text, image, audio and font files in easy formats to edit like XML, TXT, PO, PNG, WAV files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tinke</title>
      <link>/project/tinke/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 02:01:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/tinke/</guid>
      <description>Deprecated program. Superseded by Yarhl
Don&amp;rsquo;t judge the code, I wrote the whole program while learning programming 😄
    Source code Forum     GitHub GBATemp    Tinke is a program to see, convert, and edit the files of NDS games. You can see a lot of format files like images, text, sounds, fonts and textures. Furthermore it works with plugins made in NET Framework languages (C# and VB.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yarhl</title>
      <link>/project/yarhl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2018 02:01:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/yarhl/</guid>
      <description>   Website Source code Documentation     Here GitHub Here    Yarhl is a library for ROM Hacking and fan-translation projects. It provides a virtual file system, file format and format conversion features and plugin support. It&amp;rsquo;s built in C# / .NET and works in Windows, Linux and Mac OS X.
    Linux &amp;amp; Mac OS X Windows     Build &amp;amp; Test                 Quality report    Coverage    Quality Reports    Quality Details       Code Stats     </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>